golfonline.co.uk 2016-03-31

# Golfonline : Privacy and Security

Since we launched in 2000, online privacy has been a priority for us.  It’s changed a lot, but over the years we have found that it is best to do things right. We make sure that our privacy policy is in line with the law, and a recognised industry standard. As such, our privacy policy is in line with the [Data Protection Act 1998](http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/1998/29/contents).  Below are the main subjects our customers need information about, but for anything else, please feel free to contact us anytime.   

Cookies

A Cookie is a small file created by your browser and stored on your hard drive. It picks up useful bits of information about your time on our site and makes the experience smoother. For example, at GolfOnline, we use cookies to collect information about which items you are choosing whilst you shop with us, and then we place the information about the products you finally choose into the checkout, ready for you to pay for once you are ready. No other personal information is contained or transmitted in the cookie. If you reject cookies, you will be unable to place orders on the GolfOnline.co.uk website.

Security

When you place your order you are automatically connected to our secure servers using SSL 256 bit encryption. Once you enter the secure site a closed padlock will show in your browser status bar. This means that your personal and card details are fully encrypted, and remain secure across the internet and after they reach our order processing centre.

Site Reporting

We use Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to assist us in gathering broad demographic information, like for example, how many visitors we have in each European country. IP addresses are not linked to you or your personally identifiable information.

Passwords

When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected on-line, off-line and in transit. We do not store your actual password. Instead, a system know as MD5 hashing is used to ‘one-way encrypt’ your password, meaning we can only receive a correct password from you, not send your chosen password outwards from us to you or anyone else. Should you lose you password, you can void it and reset it, without worrying about it turning up in any of your mail.

Newsletters

GolfOnline.co.uk sends out regular newsletters with select discounts and offers, as well as exclusive content and product insight in conjunction with leading golfing brands. Typically we send between 1 and 2 newsletters per month to an email address of your choice. This is an opt-in system so after subscribing you will receive a confirmation email; and you can always opt-out by going to your account management section or by simply clicking the "unsubscribe" link at the bottom of a newsletter. 

This newsletter is only between us at GolfOnline, and you, our customers and subscribers. As such, we do not sell, or pass on, your information to any third parties. When subscribing to our newsletter we collect the following mandatory information: First Name, Last Name and Email Address. 

We hope you find our information and resources useful. Should you have any questions about this policy, please contact our team at [team@golfonline.co.uk](mailto:team@golfonline.co.uk?subject=Newsletter%20subscription).

Legal Notices

We have made every effort to display as accurately as possible the colours of our products that appear on the Site. However, as the actual colours you see will depend on your own system, we cannot guarantee that you will receive product with precisely the same colour as your monitor showed. All products have been fairly described and the weights, dimensions and capacities given are approximate only.

All items are subject to availability. We reserve the right to withdraw any item from sale at any time should it not meet our standards.

All information including prices are correct at the time of publishing and include VAT. We make every effort to maintain prices, although it may be necessary to change prices either up or down without notice.

The price change will be that quoted on the site at the time you place your order. However, you may find a different price should you look on our site at a different time.

We will endeavour to deliver your order within the delivery times quoted on the site. You should note restrictions described on the site with regard to last delivery dates before holiday periods (such as Christmas) and for Express deliveries in the UK and USA.

All offers are subject to merchandise availability.

Terms of Use

By accessing, browsing and/or using this site, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agreed to be bound by these terms and to comply with all applicable laws and regulations. If you do not agree these terms, please do not use this site. The GolfOnline.co.uk website makes no representation that this site or its content are appropriate or available for use in any locations outside the UK. Those who choose to access the site from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with applicable local laws. None of team of GolfOnline.co.uk or any of its directors, employees, agents or representatives will be liable for damages (including, without limitation, any compensatory, direct, indirect or consequential damages, loss of data, income or profit, loss of or damages to property and claims of third parties) arising out of or related to, and the use of, this site or its contents.

Your Consent

By providing personal information you consent to the collection and use of this information by GolfOnline.co.uk as outlined in this privacy policy. In return, we promise to adhere to European data protection legislation, and to use this information to serve you better. Data collected on this website from European visitors will not leave Europe other than in accordance with those laws. If we change this policy we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect and to what purposes.

Trademarks and Copyrights

All trademarks, service marks and companies name or logos cited herein are the property of their respective owners.

All Web site design, text, graphics are the property of GolfOnline.co.uk © 2001. All rights reserved.

External Links and User Submitted Content

This web site may contains links to other sites and user-generated content. Please be aware that GolfOnline.co.uk is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of external sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements any web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

Social Login (i.e.Login with Facebook or Google)

Social Login is a quick and easy way to login securely with your existing Google, Facebook or other known providers of this service. You will have the option to select what information you wish to share with us from the respective provider, and don't worry we do share any of your personal information with third parties without your permission. We would simply use the information passed from your provider to either register your account automatically or login securely on our website.

## **Contact Details**

We understand that most golfers do not have the time to go through pages of information on our site, so if you ever need any clarification, please contact us anytime on team@golfonline.co.uk or you can send a letter to:

Fairway of Course Ltd  
Trading as GolfOnline.co.uk  
506 - 508 Honeypot Lane  
Stanmore  
Harrow  
Middlesex  
HA7 1JS  
United Kingdom

Tel: 0208 951 6080  
Fax: 0870 460 2169
